Shrek is old.
The name, I study Tanakh.
Yes.
I study Tanakh, I promise.
You know Yermiyahu.
Yermiyahu.
Jeremiah.
Yes, yes.
You don't love people.
I love people.
And I love Tanakh too.
Yeah.
I'm curious, Yermiyahu.
Verse 7:22.
It says God did not command sacrifice.
We're not debating.
I'm not debating, I'm asking.
I want to learn Tanakh.
I don't want to, I don't want to, I don't want to...
Educate.
You go to your research world.
It's okay.
We won't win.
I'm not debating, I'm asking.
I'm asking. So the sin transfers to the chicken?
No, it's just a reminder for us to...
to repent.
It's a reminder.
It doesn't, it doesn't matter.
No, I'm really, I'm really...
And this is where it starts, and this is where it finishes.
And all liberals would not respect religion and tradition,
so it's invalid or arguments.
Yeah, I'm not a liberal.
I'm not a liberal.
I'm concerned.
To your own.
If there's no higher power, then no debate is starting.
I'm not, I believe, I believe in Hashem.
100%.
I know the Shema.
Hero is your own, the Lord our God is one.
Correct?
Yes.
I believe Hashem.
Circumcised?
In my circumcised?
That you're asking?
Yes.
My parents circumcised me.
Oh, to Prince.
Yes.
I mean, I'm not going to show you.
Where do you live?
I live in Georgia, the state of Georgia, but I'm up here visiting friends.
Which area?
In Georgia?
Augusta, Georgia, where the Southern Baptists live.
So I was raised Christian, but I...
What do you do?
I just document.
I'm a documentarian.
You're a documentarian?
Yeah, yeah, and I'm very...
How are you working now?
Currently, I'm working on a film called The Moses Scroll.
Have you heard about the Shapira Scroll?
Moses Shapira, who found the Dead Sea Scroll?
Are you familiar with the Dead Sea Scroll?
1800s?
Yeah.
I'm very fascinated with Tanakh, with the Pentateuch, so I'm asking genuine questions.
What about, you know, Hosea?
Hosea?
6 verse 6?
I desire mercy, not sacrifice?
So how does...
Is this sacrifice?
Why is this sacrifice?
What's the problem with it?
Everything's okay.
The chickens are okay.
Everything is okay.
But it's a sacrifice?
It's a sacrifice?
Go to the Smithfield and go to the meatpacking plants over there and take care of there.
I agree with you.
Those are sacrifices too.
And it's no different.
This is how society has worked ever since and nothing will change.
No amount of enlightenment will change.
People will always eat animals and this is how it was intended to be and everything is okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
But, Genesis 1:29, huh?
God's ideal is no predation.
Genesis 1:29.
That does not mean predation.
Predation is when people come and instigate other people from different religions.
People feel repressed and oppressed anti-Semitism, anti-Islamophobia, or for that matter any class system or any people from that perspective.
Racism and all this does not mean that one should be a vegetarian.
Yeah.
I agree with you.
End of discussion.
I agree with you about Chick-fil-A.
I agree with you about Chick-fil-A, but do people eat meat chickens?
It goes to the slaughterhouse.
It goes to the slaughterhouse and people eat them?
Yes, absolutely.
So, are they eating the sins?
No, they're not eating the chicken.
But the sins go in the chicken, right?
No, that's not work as well.
You do better your research.
Okay.
Can you tell me?
Where do the sins go?
It doesn't go anywhere.
You can turn chickens from the right of the right.
You've got to repent.
You don't repent.
Oh, I repent every day.
I repent and do my mikvah.
You're doing a good job.
My mikvah is baptism.
Do you have a baptism?
The mikvah?
You're doing a good job.
Okay.
So, the sins don't go in the chicken?
The sins go in the chicken or no?
It's for atonement, right?
For Yom Kippur?
It's for atonement.
It's for atonement, right?
For Yom Kippur?
It's for atonement.
I'm asking.
I know some Hebrew.
They're impressionable young people.
We're asking them a question.
They don't know.
They haven't learned.
They absolutely don't know.
Curious questions from a distant, genuine place is very dangerous.
Very dangerous.
No, I'm genuine.
But even then your question.
Hosea.
Yerumiyahu.
Yerumiyahu is my favorite prophet.
It doesn't matter.
If people who are from a certain culture with a certain belief system.
Yeah.
If young people who aren't fully educated.
But I believe in Hashim.
We're brothers.
I believe in Hashim.
It's not about brothers.
It's not about brothers or anything.
But you know Yerumiyahu.
7:22.
Yerumiyahu 7:22.
Is it numbered?
Do you know it?
Yerumiyahu 7:22.